Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Appeal of Conscience Foundation Material, 1964-2018, undated; 29 audiocassettes; 5 VHS; 52.75 Gigabytes in 6,985 computer files.; 32 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 59 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 2.5 media boxes.
  - Subseries I.E. Peace and Tolerance Conferences, 1991-2005, undated; 7 audiocassettes; 2.60 Megabytes in 86 computer files.; 2 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and .5 media box.
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Menus, Invitation, and List of Participants -- Dr. Wolfgang Schussel Dinner, 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Messages and Information Packet, 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Press, 1999-2000; 3 folders (Box 153, Folder 19, 20, Box 177, Folder 10)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Press, Messages, and List of Participants, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Program, Name Tags, and List of Participants, 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Sound Recording, undated; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - 1999 ACF Kosovo Conference on Peace and Tolerance: Vienna Declaration, 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Agenda Drafts, Correspondence, Itineraries, and Participant Lists, TW_TAM_694_ER_31
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Agenda Drafts, Participant and Invitee Lists, Itineraries, Travel Information, Program Drafts, and Speeches, TW_TAM_694_ER_30
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 156, Folder 6, 7, 18)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence -- Invitations, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence -- Invitation Responses, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence -- Jewish Attendees, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence -- Message Requests to Religious and Government Leaders, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence -- Turkish Religious and Political Leaders, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Correspondence and List of Religious Leaders, 2005, undated; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Declaration and Speeches, 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Declarations -- Signed, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 21)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Formal Invitations, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Information Packet, 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Invitations -- from the Ecumenical Patriarchate, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: List of Delegates -- Visits to Chief Rabbi Isac Haleva and the Governor of Istanbul, undated; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Lists of Invitees, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Menu and Agenda Draft, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - 2005 ACF Correspondence on Peace and Tolerance II: Name Tags, TW_TAM_694_ER_32
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Outline of ACF Report -- Ferrara, Peter, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 20)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Participant Lists
      - Digital Files, TW_TAM_694_ER_33
      - Paper Files (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Participants List, Travel Logistics, and Program Draft, TW_TAM_694_ER_29
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Press, 1994-2005, undated; 2 folders (Box 156, Folder 5, 21)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Program, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Reports and Notes -- Pre-Conference, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 19)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Sound Recordings (Box 206, Cassette 694.0011, 694.0012, Box 255, Cassette 694.0029-694.0033)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Speech, 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Speeches and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Speeches and Messages, 2 folders (Box 156, Folder 3, 4)
    - 2005 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance II: Transcripts, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 22)
    - ACF Peace and Tolerance International Conferences: Bern and Bosporus Declarations, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - ACF Peace and Tolerance International Conferences: Declarations, 1992-2005; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - ACF Peace and Tolerance International Conferences: Information Packet -- ACF, 1992-1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - ACF Peace and Tolerance International Conferences: Press, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 22)
  - Subseries I.F. Correspondence, 1964-2016, undated; 86.5 kilobytes in 2 computer files.; 8 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 15 manuscript boxes.
    This subseries contains material in the form of faxes, handwritten letters, and emails between Rabbi Arthur Schneier and ACF's administrative aides, various business and religious dignitaries, and individuals who donated to the Foundation. Of note are some letters circa 1970 between Rabbi Schneier and international rabbinical students interested in studying in the United States and the original newspaper announcement of the founding of ACF in 1965. There is a substantial amount of correspondence about sending Passover supplies to the Cuban Jewish community between the Foundation and members of the Cuban Jewish community. There are also a considerable number of newsletters and press material about the Foundation that were sent out to the Foundation's donors. Some material is in Spanish, Russian, Hebrew, or French. There is a small amount of born-digital media--two files--in this subseries.
    The material in this subseries is arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by type.
    - ACF Correspondence, 1964-1978; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Original Announcement of ACF, 1965; 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 27)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1965; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 21)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Gray, George Chairman of the Brooklyn Committee of ACF, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Letters to Donors, 1966; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1966; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 25)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Advertisement You Are Not Forsaken, Soviet Jewry, 1966; cuid2599; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Advisory Council Meeting, 1967; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1967; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1968; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 23)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Board of Trustees Agendas and Letters from Policitians, 1969-1976; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Board of Trustees and Executive Committee Meetings, 1969-1976; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 15)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1969; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1970; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Donors, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Northern Ireland Report, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 8, 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Romanian Flood Relief Fundraising, 1970; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1971-1975; 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 7, Box 209, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China, 1971-1976; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Bogdan, Ambassador Corneliu for Romania, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Drafts of Brochures, Press, and Handouts, 1971; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Tucci, Father Roberto Interview, 1971; 1 folder (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Northern Ireland, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1971; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 24)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1972; 3 folders (Box 228, Folder 6, Box 162, Folder 18, Box 209, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Planned Visit of Soviet Interfaith Delegation, 1972; 2 folders (Box 193, Folder 8, 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1972; 2 folders (Box 218, Folder 28, Box 193, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Soviet Religious Leaders Visit to the United States, 1972; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1973-1975; 5 folders (Box 228, Folder 4, 5, Box 259, Folder 2, 19, Box 209, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Brochure Drafts, 1973, undated; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Northern Ireland Project, 1973, undated; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 3, 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Possible Trip to South Africa, 1973-1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1973; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press Release about Rabbi Lubanov, of Leningrad, Death, 1973; 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United States Embassy in Soviet Russia about Chapel, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1974-1976; 2 folders (Box 162, Folder 17, Box 165, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Soviet Union Delegation, 1974; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Advisory Council, Trustees, and Officers, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Bensten, Senator Lloyd M., 1974; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1974; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Persecution of the Iranian Baha'i Community, 1974-1992; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 12, 13)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1975; 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 89, Folder 10, Box 259, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China, 1975; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 23)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Death of ACF Vice President Harold A. Bosley, 1975; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Draft of Brochures and Press, 1975, undated; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Iranian Ambassador, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Letters to Donors, 1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Moscow Central Synagogue, 1975-1982; 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1975; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 29)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Request for Aid, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1976-1977, undated; 3 folders (Box 74, Folder 10, Box 209, Folder 6, Box 283, Folder 20)
    - ACF Correspondence -- American Embassy in Moscow, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Campion, Father Donald R., S.J. ACF Trustee, 1976-1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Cancelled ACF Delegation to South Africa, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Letters to Donors, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1976; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1977-1978; 4 folders (Box 162, Folder 5, Box 165, Folder 9, Box 7, Folder 25, Box 209, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Advisory Council, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Employees, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Trustees and Officers, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Grant-in-aid Application for Eastern Europe Exchange Program, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Invitations and Event Programs with Seating Lists, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Lists of ACF Officers, Trustees, and Advisory Council, 1977, undated; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Sills, Beverly, 1977; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Visas for Possible Trip to South Africa, 1977, undated; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1978; 5 folders (Box 73, Folder 22, Box 162, Folder 14, Box 165, Folder 20, Box 7, Folder 19, Box 209, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Czech Republic, 1978-1989; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 6, 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1978-1980; 3 folders (Box 73, Folder 21, Box 257, Folder 10, Box 259, Folder 20)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press and Photographs, 1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United Nations, Non-Governmental Organizations Section, 1978; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United States Department of State, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Winter Holiday Messages, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1979; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 21, 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Board of Trustees Meetings, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Meeting Agenda, 1979; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Logistics of Shipping 300 Taleisim to Moscow Synagogue, 1979; 1 folder (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Miklos, Imre, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 228, Folder 21)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Request for Grants from the International Communications Agency, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Shanah Tovah Messages, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Winter Holiday Messages, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 228, Folder 19, Box 259, Folder 8, Box 209, Folder 10)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Newsletter, 1980, undated; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Winter Holiday Messages, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1981, undated; 3 folders (Box 250, Folder 18, Box 259, Folder 15, Box 209, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China Visits, 1981, undated; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Argentina, 1981; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Wen Wen, Deng and Yan Chang You Studying in the United States, 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 250, Folder 21, 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Gao, Professor, 1981-1989; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1982; 3 folders (Box 73, Folder 24, Box 250, Folder 17, Box 209, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Chinese Jewish Community, 1982; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Material for Press, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Duke, Angier Biddle, Notes, 1982; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Obituary Notices for Newspapers, 1982; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Grant-in-aid Application for Romanian Religious Leaders Visit to the United States, 1983; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United States Information Agency, 1983; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 228, Folder 18, Box 209, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Marriott, J.W. Jr., 1983; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Photographic Contact Sheets and Press, 1983-1985, undated; 1 folder (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Shalom, Stephen, 1983; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United States-Japan Foundation, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 25)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1984-1985; 3 folders (Box 159, Folder 16, Box 171, Folder 10, Box 209, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China, 1984-1989; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Building Renewal Lease, 1984; 1 folder (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1985; 3 folders (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 159, Folder 17, Box 171, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Board of Trustees Memos and Agenda, 1985, undated; 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 159, Folder 2, 8, Box 160, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe Report, 1985; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1985; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Richard Cohen Associates, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Romanian Representative to the United Nations, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1986; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Board of Trustees Advisory Council, 1986; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1986; 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Response to New York Times Article about Shanghai's Jews, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Rosen, Rabbi Moses, 1986-1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1987, undated; 5 folders (Box 12, Folder 3, Box 73, Folder 23, Box 230, Folder 13, Box 171, Folder 11, Box 209, Folder 15)
    - ACF Correspondence -- ACF Activities Update, 1987; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe, 1987; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Internal Memos, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Letters to Donors, 1987-1996; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Miklos, Imre, 1987; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1988; 5 folders (Box 12, Folder 4, 5, Box 225, Folder 11, Box 231, Folder 10, Box 171, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1988; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Notice of Rabbi Arthur Schneier's Appointment as an Alternate Representative of the United States of America to the United Nations General Assembly, 1988; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Romania, 1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Two Romanian Student Scholarships, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1989; 7 folders (Box 12, Folder 6-9, Box 215, Folder 4, Box 73, Folder 25, Box 171, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Pan Guang, 1989; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1989; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Romania, 1989; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1990; 5 folders (Box 12, Folder 10-13, Box 171, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1990; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence -- United States Information Agency, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1991-1993; 7 folders (Box 12, Folder 14-19, Box 171, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Egyptian Politicians, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1992; 7 folders (Box 12, Folder 20-26)
    - ACF Correspondence -- 1993 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Jewish-Chinese Affairs, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba Press, 1992; 2 folders (Box 231, Folder 14, Box 232, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1993; 7 folders (Box 12, Folder 27-32, Box 209, Folder 18)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China, 1993; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Moussa, Egyptian Foreign Minister Amre M., 1993; 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Japan Information Center, 1993; 1 folder (Box 225, Folder 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Meeting with Chinese Foreign Minister Qian Qichen, 1993; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Messages for Postponed 1993 ACF Conference on Peace and Tolerance, 1 folder (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1993; 1 folder (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Requests for Tax Information, 1993-1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Sirikit, Thailand Queen, 1993; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- World Economic Forum, 1993; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1994; 4 folders (Box 12, Folder 33, Box 225, Folder 10, Box 106, Folder 12, Box 209, Folder 19)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Bosnia and Herzegovina, 1994-1997; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - ACF Correspondence -- China, 1994; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- "Jewish Refugees in Shanghai" Film Project, 1994; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1994; 1 folder (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Terrorist Bombing of Argentine Jewish Community Offices in Buenos Aires, 1994; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1995; 2 folders (Box 231, Folder 12, Box 209, Folder 20)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Indonesia, 1995-2002; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Israel, 1995; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Jerusalem 3000, 1995; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - ACF Correspondence -- 1995 Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1996; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Israel, 1996; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Jewish-Chinese Affairs, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- The Nippon Foundation, 1996; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 22)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Press, 1996; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Secretary of State's Open Forum at the United States Department of State, 1996; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 23)
    - ACF Correspondence, 1997; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 24)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Israel, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Latvia, 1997; 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Cancelled ACF Delegation Visit to China, 1997; 2 folders (Box 233, Folder 15, 16)
    - ACF Correspondence -- Letters to Donors, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - ACF Correspondence -- 1997 Passover Shipment to Cuba, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 26)